{
  "first":{
    "question":"Are you getting exercises how do you prepare?",
    "background":"background_1",
    "person":"null",
    "face":"null",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I ask acquaintances if someone could take me to rehearsals","I don't think about future exercises at all","I mark the exercises on the calendar and I go to the exercises myself."],
    "I ask acquaintances if someone could take me to rehearsals":"tiedustelu",
    "I don't think about future exercises at all":"paniikki",
    "I mark the exercises on the calendar and I go to the exercises myself.":"yksin",
    "I ask acquaintances if someone could take me to rehearsalsColor":"green",
    "I don't think about future exercises at allColor":"red",
    "I mark the exercises on the calendar and I go to the exercises myself.Color":"green"},
  "tiedustelu":{
    "question":"You get your acquaintance caught and he suggests a schedule when you are ahead of time.",
    "background":"background_6",
    "person":"null",
    "face":"null",
    "fore":"fore_7",
    "answers":["No way!","Ok","I skip the exercises"],
    "No way!":"first",
    "Ok":"yhdessa",
    "I skip the exercises":"null",
    "No way!Color":"red",
    "OkColor":"green",
    "I skip the exercisesColor":"yellow"},
  "paniikki":{
    "question":"You should go to the exercises and you have nothing prepared.",
    "background":"background_2",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I gather all the goods together and leave","I skip the exercises","I start calling acquaintances who could take me to rehearsals."],
    "I gather all the goods together and leave":"yksin",
    "I skip the exercises":"null",
    "I start calling acquaintances who could take me to rehearsals.":"yhdessa",
    "I gather all the goods together and leaveColor":"green",
    "I skip the exercisesColor":"yellow",
    "I start calling acquaintances who could take me to rehearsals.Color":"yellow"},
  "yksin":{
    "question":"Which vehicle do you leave?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["my car","by bus","shovel"],
    "my car":"auto",
    "by bus":"bussi",
    "shovel":"first",
    "my carColor":"green",
    "by busColor":"green",
    "shovelColor":"red"},
  "yhdessa":{
    "question":"On the workout day you go to wait for your ride and your acquaintance announces that it is a little late. How do you work?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I was worried about how the whole plan would go to waste.","I count the new schedule in my head.","I'm waiting in peace"],
    "I was worried about how the whole plan would go to waste.":"kaveri",
    "I count the new schedule in my head.":"kaveri",
    "I'm waiting in peace":"kaveri",
    "I was worried about how the whole plan would go to waste.Color":"red",
    "I count the new schedule in my head.Color":"yellow",
    "I'm waiting in peaceColor":"green"},
  "auto":{
    "question":"Which route do you choose?",
    "background":"background_3",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_surprised",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["The fastest so I can prepare in peace.","The calmest, for I am in no hurry.","I don't leave because I forgot my workout gear.","Speeding time to the training site."],
    "The fastest so I can prepare in peace.":"paikalla",
    "The calmest, for I am in no hurry.":"paikalla",
    "I don't leave because I forgot my workout gear.":"first",
    "Speeding time to the training site.":"paikalla",
    "The fastest so I can prepare in peace.Color":"green",
    "The calmest, for I am in no hurry.Color":"green",
    "I don't leave because I forgot my workout gear.Color":"yellow",
    "Speeding time to the training site.Color":"red"},
  "bussi":{
    "question":"You arrived at the internship bus stop. What are you doing?",
    "background":"background_1",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I'll be right back","I go to practice place.","I go to the internship as slowly as I can."],
    "I'll be right back":"null",
    "I go to practice place.":"paikalla",
    "I go to the internship as slowly as I can.":"paikalla",
    "I'll be right backColor":"red",
    "I go to practice place.Color":"green",
    "I go to the internship as slowly as I can.Color":"yellow"},
  "kaveri":{
    "question":"Your acquaintance will come to pick you up.",
    "background":"background_3",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I complain all the way that I am late.","I silently all the way.","I demand, after familiarizing myself, to drive at speed.","I talk to my acquaintances normally."],
    "I complain all the way that I am late.":"paikalla",
    "I silently all the way.":"paikalla",
    "I demand, after familiarizing myself, to drive at speed.":"paikalla",
    "I talk to my acquaintances normally.":"paikalla",
    "I complain all the way that I am late.Color":"red",
    "I silently all the way.Color":"green",
    "I demand, after familiarizing myself, to drive at speed.Color":"red",
    "I talk to my acquaintances normally.Color":"green"},
  "paikalla":{
    "question":"You have arrived at the intership what do you do?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I put training equipment.","I wait until the last minute and change only, then practice the gear on.","I go to toilet."],
    "I put training equipment.":"alkaa",
    "I wait until the last minute and change only, then practice the gear on.":"alkaa",
    "I go to toilet.":"tokana",
    "I put training equipment.Color":"green",
    "I wait until the last minute and change only, then practice the gear on.Color":"yellow",
    "I go to toilet.Color":"green"},
  "tokana":{
    "question":"You go to the bathroom what do you do?",
    "background":"background_3",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I will take care of the matter and fill the water bottle if necessary.","I'll take care of it.","I lock up in the bathroom and don't go to exercises."],
    "I will take care of the matter and fill the water bottle if necessary.":"vaihto",
    "I'll take care of it.":"vaihto",
    "I lock up in the bathroom and don't go to exercises.":"null",
    "I will take care of the matter and fill the water bottle if necessary.Color":"green",
    "I'll take care of it.Color":"green",
    "I lock up in the bathroom and don't go to exercises.Color":"red"},
  "vaihto":{
    "question":"You come from the toilet what do you do next?",
    "background":"background_3",
    "person":"null",
    "face":"null",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I change myself to training equipment on.","I wait for the last minute and change, then practice the gear on.","I'm going home anyway.","I'm going home because I'm ill."],
    "I change myself to training equipment on.":"alkaa",
    "I wait for the last minute and change, then practice the gear on.":"alkaa",
    "I'm going home anyway.":"null",
    "I'm going home because I'm ill.":"ilmoitus",
    "I change myself to training equipment on.Color":"green",
    "I wait for the last minute and change, then practice the gear on.Color":"yellow",
    "I'm going home anyway.Color":"red",
    "I'm going home because I'm ill.Color":"green"},
  "alkaa":{
    "question":"You go to the training area what do you do?",
    "background":"background_1",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["to practice","play on the phone"],
    "to practice":"harjoitusloppu",
    "play on the phone":"harjoitusloppu",
    "to practiceColor":"green",
    "play on the phoneColor":"red"},
  "ilmoitus":{
    "question":"How do you leave?",
    "background":"background_1",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_sad",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I inform the coach \/ instructor that I am in pain.","I don't tell anyone anything.","I call an acquaintance and explain the situation."],
    "I inform the coach \/ instructor that I am in pain.":"harjoitusloppu",
    "I don't tell anyone anything.":"harjoitusloppu",
    "I call an acquaintance and explain the situation.":"harjoitusloppu",
    "I inform the coach \/ instructor that I am in pain.Color":"green",
    "I don't tell anyone anything.Color":"yellow",
    "I call an acquaintance and explain the situation.Color":"green"},
  "harjoitusloppu":{
    "question":"You leave the exercises.",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I call the pacifier and ask them to take me.","I go home by bus.","I go home some other way.","I will stand and I will not go anywhere, though i should."],
    "I call the pacifier and ask them to take me.":"null",
    "I go home by bus.":"null",
    "I go home some other way.":"null",
    "I will stand and I will not go anywhere, though i should.":"null",
    "I call the pacifier and ask them to take me.Color":"green",
    "I go home by bus.Color":"green",
    "I go home some other way.Color":"green",
    "I will stand and I will not go anywhere, though i should.Color":"red"},
}